Name=XenoPlanets
Author=Klaxons, Обер, Mik, Людмила Токмакова, Xenomorphchyma
Conflict=KlaxonsBG, XenoBG, ExpPlanets, EvoBG, EvoBG2, RefPhaeton
Dependence=
Priority=6
Section=XenoMods
SectionEng=XenoMods
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=[Xeno] Новые домашние планеты, системные фоны и широкоформатные 4К-фоны незаселённых планет
FullDescription=XenoPlanets заменяет XenoBG, ExpPlanets и EvoBG одним самостоятельным модом.
FullDescription=<br>
FullDescription=Добавляет ровно по одной необитаемой планете в домашние системы пяти рас: Гархарл, Чешилан, Нептун, Тристерию и Дээву. Перед созданием скрипт проверяет, нет ли планеты с таким именем в нужной системе.
FullDescription=<br>
FullDescription=Также включает девять дополнительных фонов звёздных систем и все широкоформатные 4К-фоны XenoBG.

SmallDescriptionEng=[Xeno] New home-system planets, system backgrounds and widescreen 4K uninhabited-planet backgrounds
FullDescriptionEng=XenoPlanets replaces XenoBG, ExpPlanets and EvoBG with one standalone mod.
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=Adds exactly one uninhabited planet to each race home system: Garharl, Cheshilan, Neptune, Tristeria and Deeva. The script checks the target system for an existing planet with the same name before creating it.
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=Also includes nine additional star-system backgrounds and all widescreen 4K backgrounds from XenoBG.
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=230,20,0>Do not enable ExpPlanets, EvoBG, EvoBG2 or RefPhaeton at the same time: they contain their own scripts that add the same planets.</color>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,132,15>The mod does not modify Rangers.exe and does not require a native loader.</color>
